It's like they wanna die. Too easy.
Well. I'm loving every second
of this. so I say keep 'em coming!
I'm not sure which ones
are the true beasts here.
Even missing an arm.
Chiyul's a beast himself.
Okay. that's it for this group.
It's impressive how much
stronger you've gotten. Jinwoo.
And that dagger's
also pretty striking.
Gotta say I'm really
impressed with you. too.
You fought. but didn't need me
to heal you even once.
Yeah. guess I didn't. huh?
Maybe we can get through this
without anybody needing my help.
Still. having you here is nice.
He's changed. and not just his looks.
There's a different aura about him.
Like slaying beasts
is nothing to him now.
Did you start learning martial arts?
Let's keep it moving. people.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
We've got a choice to make.
The dungeon's been
easier than expected.
Should be fine to split
into three groups.
It'll up the risk factor if we do. but
we would clear this thing a lot sooner.
The threat's low. so sure.
I'll take the prisoners
down the path on the right.
If you find the boss chamber.
send someone to let us know.
Thanks to my enhanced
perception. it's obvious.
The boss is down there.
These goblins weren't
getting me much XP anyway.
Mister Song. I say we
take the path on the left.
Sounds good to me.
You and I'll take the middle. then.
Right. Let's go.
Hmm.
Won't have any problems
if it's just goblins.
All I want is to clear
this thing in one piece.
I'm sure we'll be fine.
If the Weakest Hunter signed up for
this. how dangerous can it really be?
Except. that's exactly what we
thought before. and well. you know...
Speaking of...
I've decided that
when this raid's over.
I'm gonna apologize to Jinwoo.
Hasn't it been bugging you?
How we ran away.
Not only are we pro hunters.
we're grown men.
We ran for the sake of our
families. but he was one of our own.
and we still left him there to die.
It's about time
we swallowed our pride.
True hunters wouldn't brush it off.
Do you think he'll forgive us?
No. not a chance.
But that's not gonna stop me.
Come on. still got work to do.
What a joke!
This isn't even a challenge.
-That all of them?
-Shocked by how fast it was?
I wanna make some more heads roll!
-What if you were facing humans?
-What?
Could you kill them as easily?
A kill's a kill. I don't
see no difference.
Yeah. S'all the same shit.
You wanted to talk.
Three men. assaulted my daughter.
She hanged herself because of it. and
my wife was hospitalized from the shock.
And yet somehow. the three of them
will be allowed to walk free in a few years.
like nothing ever happened!
To top it off. they're hunters!
They can participate in raids while
they're detained and reduce their sentences!
Tell me in what world is that fair?
Where they roam free. but my
daughter never comes home!
What's this?
Three billion. right here.
I'll beg you.
If that's what it takes.
Just please kill them!
No one has to know.
What happens in a dungeon
stays in the dungeon!
So. please...!
Please do this for me!
Here's what I'll say when
I talk with the inspectors.
A hundred goblins appeared. and killed
all three of you in a very brutal fashion.
This path is winding around so much it feels
like we might just be going in circles.
Could be. we got the dud cave.
But. oh. well.
Somebody help me!
Were you hoping for a quick death?
Well. no such luck. 'cause I was
asked to make you suffer first.
as much as I could.
W-What the hell's going on here?
Ah. Seems the paths are connected.
So if you're here. I guess that would
mean the left path led to the boss' lair.
-Thanks for the directions.
-Please! You gotta sa--
Slight change of plans.
but it's fine.
That Taeshik Kang guy visited me
in the hospital with his superior.
Hopefully. he won't
remember me. though.
-C'mon!
-Right!
What the hell were
they attacked by...
Jeongho!
What happened here?
Huh?
Mister Kim.
Joohee. heal him.
Hurry and do it!
Huh! O-Okay!
Mister Kim! Please hang on!
His wounds weren't made
by a magic beast.
Those cuts are too clean.
and several look like
killing strokes pulled
at the last second.
Stop it. Joohee.
I'm not gonna make it.
What are you talking about?
You have a family that needs you.
Dying isn't an option. So no.
You can't just die now.
I won't allow it. you're gonna live.
How can I keep blaming you
if you don't?
I'm so sorry.
I wish I had more than words.
Saw this playing out
much differently in my head.
I was gonna give you
a proper apology.
But know I am sorry. kid.
I really mean it.
Goodbye. Sangshik.
Whoa. you're a fast one.
Thought I'd save myself some
trouble by taking out the healer first.
But it seems you managed
to delay the inevitable.
Mister Kang?
Are you behind this?
It's possible.
But why? You're from the Association!
-You won't get away with murder!
-I might with the perfect story.
I was gonna say that a horde of
goblins was to blame for this little mess.
but how about this new angle?
The prisoners were plotting an escape
from the start. They killed you all!
And then they made the mistake of ambushing
me while I was busy fighting the boss.
But they soon found out
they were sorely outmatched.
and that's why
I was the sole survivor.
Well. guys? Think they'll buy it?
You piece of trash.
Though you've improved.
you won't win. I'll have to fight.
I'm borrowing this. Sangshik.
Been a while since I raised
a sword against a man.
He's one rank above me. but still!
Joohee. could you cast
a physical strength buff on me?
Uh. yes!
Assassin types
tend to have weak defenses.
I'll exploit his.
A washed-up mage like you is
suddenly relying on strength instead?
This is bound to go well.
I'm a swordsman right now.
I'll show you.
Your hunter abilities are magic-focused.
so that sword won't do you much good!
Hu-hah!
This has-been's still
full of surprises!
Look who's got moves. Wow.
And it's not even the buff
that's doing it.
You've refined those skills!
For a split second. Mister
Song caught up to him.
If he was a little faster.
As quick as you are precise. I can see
why you ditched your magic for the sword
Even so. you have your limitations.
That pain-in-the-ass healer.
She dies first after all.
You really turned your back
on an armed opponent?
You're certainly not an average
old fart. I'll give you that much.
I train an S-Rank hunter with a blade!
I won't be beaten by yours!
It's true you're skilled. but those
pesky limitations still stunt you.
Did you honestly think
that a mage with a sword
and strength buff could
beat an assassin hunter?
Here. I've got you!
No!
Fitting that your healer
is useless. too.
Later. pops.
Did it work?
You took up that sword to make
me lower my guard against magic.
All so you could blast me
when I went for the kill.
Slick for a senile old bastard.
Just not slick enough.
I'm finished!
Now die.
Again? Who are you?
Jinwoo Sung.
E-Rank Hunter.
E-Rank?
You think I'm stupid?
Jinwoo. the way you moved.
Where'd that come from?
I could see a power type being
able to block that. even at E-Rank.
But your reaction time is insane
and to pull it off twice
you'd need an assassin build.
You're build isn't
what matters. though.
Because you've been
hiding your skills.
Your little group seems
to know each other.
That rules out you being a false
ranker. they don't let witnesses live.
Which. of course.
can only mean one thing.
-A second awakening.
-Is that really true?
He reawakened?
So then. it must've happened
after the double dungeon!
Double dungeon?
Wait. Is he that pathetic E-Rank?
But he looks and acts like
a different person now.
And the mana meter only read
ten when we tested him again.
If he reawakened. it was afterwards.
So how'd he survive
the double dungeon?
In any case...
it's clear you're still
lacking experience.
Allow me to give you
a master class in hunting.
I would prefer an explanation.
You mean for killing the convicts?
They assaulted someone
and it drove her to suicide.
The grieving father
asked me to avenge her.
They weren't adequately punished.
so it's a bit of social justice.
No. it's not the criminals
I'm asking about.
Why kill Mister Kang and Mister Kim?
If it was to silence them. you
didn't have to resort to torture.
But that's exactly what you did.
You toyed with them.
"Bit of social justice?" Yeah. right.
That's not what motivates you.
Sure. I can take out
three criminals. easy.
But you've got the
wrong idea. I'm afraid.
Thing is. B-Ranks like me.
we're. uh. "top shelf." if you will.
So why do I work for jack at the Association
when plenty of major guilds want me?
I'll tell you. I enjoy killing.
And it's far more fun killing
people than it is killing beasts!
A reawakened E-Rank
has his limits. too!
Too slow.
Impressive.
Look at that agility!
He's nothing like the Jinwoo
I remember!
Nothing at all!
-He's as fast as me!
We've got the same build.
and similar skill levels.
but I have more experience
battling high-ranked enemies.
And that's why you're going
to lose this fight!
Well. you do have some grit.
Sorry.
But think you could be
a little less bloodthirsty?
See? Even the system's noticed now.
Huh?
Actually. I should be grateful.
The system's given me another
reason to make sure you die.
The system?
What's he mean?
I'm the one who has
the advantage here.
He got even faster! Wait!
His dagger can inflict poison?
You wanna see something real special?
He vanished!
I should be undetectable.
you perceptive bastard.
This is the Stealth skill. It hides
my form. sounds. and scent.
Only a select few assassin
hunters can even use this ability.
Of course. no one knows
I'm one of them.
Any guesses why? Go on!
People have seen me use it. but none
of them have ever lived to tell the tale.
How's that tendon. by the way?
-I'll heal you. Jinwoo!
-Keep your hands to yourself!
Be patient and wait
your turn. you're next.
Jinwoo's bound to be exhausted!
Think you can dodge my
next strike with that injured leg?
-'Cause I don't.
-Hey.
Are you done talking now?
Full recovery.
No.
He healed in an instant!
I've never heard of a combat hunter
who could use healing magic. too.
What else can he do?
I can't read him.
I just know he's dangerous!
That's another of my emotions gone.
I don't even need to get
angry to kill filth like you.
I get it now. You've also killed
people before. haven't you?
So we're in the same biz!
I see.
He must've had to make a number
of grave decisions in a very short time.
And it changed more than
just his appearance.
Awakenings. They granted humans unthinkable
power and turned the world on its head.
Laws and ethics
don't mean shit in here.
We hunters make the rules.
Therefore. the strongest
come out on top.
Hang on!
Is he tracking me from my bloodlust?
But he still can't pinpoint
me exactly!
This power!
No. It can't be!
Wait. What the hell?
You asked why
I killed those other two.
The answer's pretty simple.
We thrive in combat.
so normal morals don't apply.
And you're just the same.
Goes for all hunters.
Basically. we're
killing machines. right?
So I'll die.
'Cause it's natural selection.
The strongest one makes
the rules and I lost to you.
But what the hell are you?
An assassin class
with healing and debuff magic.
It's unheard of.
It is. Actually. I also wanna
know what the hell I am.
I know whatever you are.
it's not an E-Rank.
and after killing me. your little
charade is over. so why not come clean?
All right. then.
I am a hunter who gets stronger
with every battle.
Then your shadow must stretch
into some really nasty places.
Oh. you'll probably get as
strong as those places are dark.
I suggest you watch it. though.
If you gaze for long into an abyss.
the abyss. gazes also into you.
He's right.
The strength I have now is incomparable
to my old self. and for some reason...
the stronger I get. the more I feel
something inside of me falling apart.
Thank you!
You saved us again!
I'm just so blown away.
Survived another near-death
experience thanks to you.
Yeah. well. go on ahead and
start making your way out of here.
I'll handle the boss.
What? All by yourself?
On second thought. you do that.
It's a shame we can't give Sangshik
and Jeongho proper burials. though.
We'll wait for you outside.
Manager Woo!
I heard the report.
Where are they?
Right this way.
I can't believe Taeshik Kang was covertly
going on killing sprees all this time.
He always struck me
as a little sketchy.
but as his supervisor.
I was too careless.
These are the survivors.
That one.
He's the E-Rank hunter from before.
He hit quite a growth spurt.
-Huh?
-Good to see you again.
You're inspector. um...
Jinchul Woo.
You'll receive a formal apology
for what Taeshik put you through.
But. first things first...
let's address the main issue.
Which of you actually defeated him?
Guess I really can't keep
my secret any longer.
Which means. I'm gonna have to call
up Jinho and cancel our arrangement.
It was me.
I'm the one responsible
for killing Taeshik Kang.
Then. would you kindly
remind me what rank you are?
C-Rank. sir.
And could you explain.
how you achieved your victory?
Why. with my healer's help. right?
Um...
Ah. I see.
Her buffs must've been pretty
powerful to give you an edge.
Taeshik was one
of the strongest B-Ranks.
By all accounts. a C-Rank mage
shouldn't have stood a chance.
Very well.
I'll need to write this incident up.
so if you could please come with me.
Can't get cocky just
because I beat that maniac.
I couldn't tell before.
but this guy is an A-Rank.
As I am. I'd be helpless against him.
Sorry if I overstepped
my bounds by doing that.
I imagine you've got
a pretty good reason
for keeping your true
strength hidden. though.
Well. I owe you my life. so let's
just call this payback. shall we?
Three hours later. the man who
hired Taeshik Kang to kill the prisoners
turned himself in. which confirmed
that we acted in self-defense.
What a day. huh?
-Jinwoo.
-Huh?
We had a deal.
You remember it. right?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org